<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keaton Markey | Portfolio Website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Keaton Markey | Portfolio Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leading Indicators</title>
      <link>/2023/10/11/leading-indicators/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/10/11/leading-indicators/</guid>
      <description>Here is a demo app for a project to locate leading indicators for a local car dealership.
This data has been synthetically generated by MOSTLY AI.
Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a portfolio website for me, Keaton Markey. I am a data analyst with a passion for people and health. This website was created to showcase projects that I have finished and projects that I&amp;rsquo;m still working on. Feel free to reach out if you have any questions or are interested in my work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of Mental Illness</title>
      <link>/2023/05/23/the-state-of-mental-illness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/05/23/the-state-of-mental-illness/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the past couple of years, during a global period of isolation, suffering, and uncertainty, mental health has increasingly become a concern for everyone. Poor mental health represents a host of massive issues in the United States:
Suicide, the most severe outcome of mental health challenges, is the second-leading cause of death among people aged 10-34. The importance of mental health cannot be overstated when it comes to saving lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R, the tidyverse, and Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/2022/12/01/r-the-tidyverse-and-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/12/01/r-the-tidyverse-and-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial was prepared for a light overview of R, some of its capabilities, and what machine learning looks like using the {glm} and {caret} packages. It is assumed that you have some knowledge of programming concepts, maybe some statistics, but not necessarily any experience with R or ML.
Introduction R is an integrated suite of software facilities built by statisticians used for
data manipulation
calculation
graphics
data handling and storage</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
